<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on espositic</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on espositic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>it-it</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Emerging Pattern Miner</title>
      <link>/posts/emerging-pattern-miner/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/emerging-pattern-miner/</guid>
      <description>EPMiner EPMiner è un applicativo che ci permette di scoprire Pattern Frequenti e Pattern Emergenti, partendo da una collezione di transazioni. EPMiner implementa l&amp;rsquo;algoritmo di Data Mining Apriori. Per la scoperta di Pattern Frequenti dovremo inserire la frequenza minima, anche detta supporto. Una volta trovati i Pattern Emergenti possiamo andare alla scoperta di Pattern Emergenti, qui dovremo invece inserire il tasso di crescita minimo, anche detto growrate.
L&amp;rsquo;applicativo si suddivide in due moduli, che sono rispettivamente la parte Server e la parte Client del programma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dama</title>
      <link>/posts/dama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dama/</guid>
      <description>La Dama implementata in Java. Since about that time, war had been literally continuous, though strictly speaking it had not always been the same war. For several months during his childhood there had been confused street fighting in London itself, some of which he remembered vividly.
Inside the flat a fruity voice was reading out a list of figures which had something to do with the production of pig iron. The voice came from an oblong metal plaque like a dulled mirror which formed part of the surface of the right-hand wall.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
